Guide to the Jean Webster Papers, 1876–1982 (bulk 1900-1916)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series II. Writings
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act II, 1913; (1st draft, corrected TS 53 p.) (Folder 12.9)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act II, 1913; (TS, 66 p.) (Folder 12.10)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act III, fragment, 1913; (copy 1, TS, 9 p.) (Folder 12.11)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act III, 1913; (copy 2, TS, 56 p.) (Folder 12.12)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act III, 1913; (copy 3, TS, 54 p.) (Folder 12.13)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act III, 1913; (copy 4, TS, 54 p.) (Folder 13.1)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act III, various versions and portions, 1913; (TS, 26 p.) (Folder 13.2)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act III, various versions and portions, 1913; (TS/MS, 56 p.) (Folder 13.3)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act III, various versions and portions, 1913; (TS/MS, 53 p.) (Folder 13.4)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act III, various versions and portions, 1913; (TS/MS, 46 p.) (Folder 13.5)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act IV, copy 1, 1913; (TS, 36 p.) (Folder 13.6)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act IV, copy 2, 1913; (TS, 35 p.) (Folder 13.7)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act IV, copy 3, 1913; (TS, 37 p.) (Folder 13.8)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act IV, copy 4, 1913; (TS, 35 p.) (Folder 13.9)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, "old version," Act IV, fragment, 1913; (TS, 9 p.) (Folder 13.10)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act I, 1913-1914; (TS w/notes, 46 p.) (Folder 13.11)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act I, revised scenes, 1913-1914; (TS, 22 p.) (Folder 13.12)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Acts I and II, revisions, 1913-1914; (TS/MS, 16 p.) (Folder 13.13)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act II, 1913-1914; (corrected TS, 58 p. carbon copy) (Folder 14.1)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act III, 1913-1914; (corrected TS, 49 p. carbon copy) (Folder 14.2)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act III, revisions of some scenes, 1913-1914; (TS, 55 p., 1 draft) (Folder 14.3)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act IV, 1913-1914; (TS, 29 p., carbon copy) (Folder 14.4)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act IV, 1913-1914; (TS, 17 p.) (Folder 14.5)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act IV, 1913-1914; (TS, 28 p.) (Folder 14.6)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act IV, 1913-1914; (TS, 20 p.) (Folder 14.7)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act I, 1914; (TS, 36 p., carbon copy) (Folder 14.8)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act II, 1914; (TS, 42 p., carbon copy) (Folder 14.9)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act III, 1914; (TS w/notes, 23 p. carbon copy) (Folder 14.10)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act IV, 1914; (TS w/notes, 17 p. carbon copy) (Folder 14.11)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act I, 1914; (prompt copy, TS, 56 p.) (Folder 14.12)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act I, 1914; (ribbon copy, TS, 41 p.) (Folder 15.1)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act II, 1914; (ribbon copy, TS, 52 p.) (Folder 15.2)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act III, 1914; (ribbon copy, TS, 29 p.) (Folder 15.3)
  - Daddy Long-Legs, Act IV, 1914; (ribbon copy, TS, 23 p.) (Folder 15.4)
  - "Daddy Long-Legs," poem by Oliver Herford, 1916; (MS, 2 p.) (Folder 15.5)
  - Dear Enemy, plot outline, opening scene, ca. 1913-1915; (MS/TS, 6 p.) (Folder 15.6)
  - Blackmail scenario for a short story, n.d.; (MS, 70 p.) (Folder 15.7)
  - "Camping Farce,", n.d.; (MS, 24 p.) (Folder 15.8)
  - "Carnival House," notes, n.d.; (notebook, MS, 5 p.) (Folder 15.9)
  - "Carnival House," reading notes, n.d.; (notebook, 5 p.) (Folder 15.10)
  - "Carnival House," misc. notes, n.d.; (MS, 19 p.) (Folder 15.11)
  - "Carnival House," partial draft, n.d.; (MS, 16 p.) (Folder 16.1)
  - "Carnival House," plot outline, partial first draft see also JW's notebooks 19.1, 19.5, 19.6, 19.7, n.d.; (TS/MS, 66 p.) (Folder 16.2)
  - "Carnival House," see also JW's notebooks 19.1, 19.5, 19.6, 19.7
  - "The City,", n.d.; (MS, 5 p., fragments) (Folder 16.3)
  - "Copley Silence,", n.d.; (MS, 1 p., notes) (Folder 16.4)
  - Story beginning: "Fra Antonio as he worked among the monastery vines...,", n.d.; (MS, 10 p., 1 draft) (Folder 16.5)
  - "Garrett Meldrum Yellow Journalist,", n.d.; (TS w/notes, 54 p., 1 draft) (Folder 16.6)
  - "Good Samaritan,", n.d., possibly 1906-1908; (MS, 44 p., 1 draft) (Folder 16.7)
  - "Insomnia,", n.d.; (TS, 23 p., 1 draft) (Folder 16.8)
  - "Jervis Cassidy,", n.d.; (MS, 45 p., notes, fragment) (Folder 16.9)
  - "Jervis Cassidy,", n.d.; (unfinished TS, 44 p.) (Folder 16.10)
  - "The Kandy Road,", (MS, 8 p., notes) (Folder 16.11)
  - "Kate Fanshaw,", n.d.; (MS, 34 p., 1 draft, fragment) (Folder 17.1)
  - "Kingdom of Millarky,", n.d.; (MS, 16 p., notes) (Folder 17.2)
  - Knowlton Farm story, n.d.; (MS, 25 p., 1 draft, fragments) (Folder 17.3)
  - "The Last Night Out,", n.d.; (MS, 36 p., 2 drafts, fragments) (Folder 17.4)
  - "Out in Rome," Harper's Bazar, n.d.; (TS, 6 p.,) (Folder 17.5)
  - "Quadrangle,", n.d.; (MS, 4 p., dialogue scenario) (Folder 17.6)
  - Sing-Sing: copy of interview with Jean Webster, n.d.; (TS, 7 p, 1 draft) (Folder 17.7)
  - "Someday Susan,", n.d.; (MS, 53 p., 1 draft, notes) (Folder 17.8)
  - "Someday Susan,", n.d.; (MS, 75 p., 1 draft) (Folder 17.9)
  - Untitled, n.d.; (MS, 10 p., fragments) (Folder 17.10)
  - Untitled, n.d.; (MS, 2 p., fragments) (Folder 17.11)
  - Untitled, n.d.; (MS, 2 p., fragments) (Folder 17.12)
  - "Woman Who Poisoned Her Husband,", (MS, 12 p., opening) (Folder 17.13)
- Series III. Notes and Notebooks
  - Childhood and School Notebooks
    - Alice J. Webster's autograph album, includes double signature of S.L. Clemens and Mark Twain, 1887-1894; (55 p.) (Folder 17.14)
    - Idioms — Latin, French, Italian, n.d.; (MS, 16 p.) (Folder 17.15)
    - Order of Shakespeare's Plays — chronological list, quotations from each play up to "Troilus and Cressida,", (MS, 123 p.) (Folder 17.16)
    - Jean Webster Vocabulary — alphabetical list of unusual words, n.d.; (MS, 136 p.) (Folder 18.1)
    - Literary Technique endorsed "A.J.C. Webster,", Vassar to 1903; (MS, 198 p.) (Folder 18.2)
    - Ideal Novel — in general removed from 18.2, (MS, 6 p.) (Folder 18.3)
  - Travel Journals, Story Ideas, etc.
    - Original, 1901-1905; (MS, 114 p.) (Folder 18.4)
    - Reading Notes, Fall 1901; (MS, 51 p.) (Folder 18.5)
    - Jean Webster 1901 — copy of "Original" sayings, story suggestions and references, 1901, n.d.; (MS, 118 p.) (Folder 18.6)
    - Record of submissions and publications, 1902-1914; (29 p.) (Folder 19.1)
    - Applied Vocabulary I — maxims, witticisms, etc. selected from JW's reading, n.d.; (MS, 88 p.) (Folder 19.2)
    - Applied Vocabulary II, Dec 1902; (MS, 112 p.) (Folder 19.3)
    - Applied Vocabulary III, n.d.; (MS, 104 p.) (Folder 19.4)
    - College Settlement Notes, Apr 1903; (MS, 9 p.) (Folder 19.5)
    - Journal of visit to Naples, Rome, and Palestrina, 18 Nov 1903 - 4 Apr 1904; (MS, 132 p.) (Folder 19.6)
    - Journal of visit to Palestrina, 4-17 Apr 1904; (MS, 138 p.) (Folder 19.7)
    - Journal of visit to Palestrina, 17-24 Apr 1904; (MS, 86 p.) (Folder 19.8)
    - Proverbs and quotes from various authors, ca. Dec1904; (MS, 138 p.) (Folder 20.1)
    - Journal of world tour, Nov 15, 1906-Mar 21, 1907; (MS, 187 p.) (Folder 20.2)
    - India — reading notes on India, ca. 1906/1907-1916; (MS, 84 p.) (Folder 20.3)
    - India: see also Ceylon Tea Plantation play
    - Untitled notes about Ceylon, 1907; (MS, 2 p.) (Folder 20.4)
    - Short Story Bibliography — authors, titles, critics' comments, ?-1907; (MS/TS, 108 p.) (Folder 21.1)
    - Irish Notes — reading/travel notes, 1912; (MS, 11 p.) (Folder 21.2)
    - Ireland — reading/travel notes, 1912; (2 notebooks, 59 p.) (Folder 21.3)
    - Ireland — reading/travel notes, 1912; (MS, 86 p.) (Folder 21.4)
    - Irish Reading Notes, 1912; (MS, 51 p.) (Folder 21.5)
    - Travel journal of Ireland trip, June 29-Aug 9, 1912; (MS, 51 p.) (Folder 21.6)
    - Half-a-Loaf — scenario, plot outline, Oct-Dec 1912; (MS, 106 p.) (Folder 22.1)
    - Reading notes, ca.1913; (MS, 161 p.) (Folder 22.2)
    - Scotch Dialect — word lists, etc. compiled as an aid to Dear Enemy, Feb-Mar 1913; (MS, 58 p.) (Folder 22.3)
    - Dramatic Notes, 1916; (MS, 14 p.) (Folder 22.4)
    - Address books, up to 1916; (3 books) (Folder 22.5)
  - Undated notes and notebooks
    - "II. Dramatic Criticism" — sequel to "Plays I," Folder 24.4, reading notes, n.d.; (MS, 95 p.) (Folder 23.1)
    - Dialogue - Technique - Names, n.d.; (MS, 47 p.) (Folder 23.2)
    - Dramatic bibliography, notes, comments on contemporary plays, n.d.; (MS, 39 p.) (Folder 23.3)
    - Exercise, etc. notes on physical exercise and medications, (MS, 29 p.) (Folder 23.4)
    - Story fragments, plot outlines, reading notes, n.d.; (MS, 48 p.) (Folder 23.5)
    - Plot Outlines, n.d.; (MS, 119 p.) (Folder 23.6)
    - Ugolina story fragments, n.d.; (MS, 20 p.) (Folder 23.7)
    - Kingdom of Millarky — list of novels, phrases, brief plot outline, n.d.; (MS, 7 p.) (Folder 24.1)
    - Notes on Alcoholism for Half a Loaf, n.d.; (MS, 106 p.) (Folder 24.2)
    - Notes on Neuresthenia and Dipsomania for Over Jordan — reading notes from medical authorities, (MS, 63 p.) (Folder 24.3)
    - Plays I — reading notes, comments about modern dramatists from recent works of criticism, (MS, 137 p.) (Folder 24.4)
    - Plays — Original Plots — stories suitable for dramatization, n.d.; (MS, 84 p.) (Folder 24.5)
    - Untitled fragments, n.d.; (MS, 10 p.) (Folder 24.6)
- Series IV. Clippings, Press Notices, Playbills
  - Reviews of JW's books, articles, etc., 1903-1907; (10 items) (Folder 25.1)
  - Much Ado About Peter — reviews, Feb-Nov 1909; (89 items) (Folder 25.2)
  - Much Ado About Peter — advertisements, Spring 1909; (2 items) (Folder 25.3)
  - Just Patty — reviews, 1911; (2 items) (Folder 25.4)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — reviews, articles, etc., 1912-1914; (30 items photocopies) (Folder 25.5)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — reviews, articles, etc., 1914-1965; (3 items originals) (Folder 25.6)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — reviews, articles, etc., 1915; (24 items, photocopies) (Folder 25.7)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — reviews, articles, etc., Jan-Apr 1916; (46 items, photocopies) (Folder 25.8)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — reviews, articles, etc., Apr-May 1916; (58 items, photocopies) (Folder 25.9)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — reviews, articles, etc., July-Sep 1916; (18 items, photocopies) (Folder 25.10)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — reviews, articles, etc., 1917-1971, n.d.; (31 items, photocopies) (Folder 25.11)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — playbills, programs, 1915-1931, n.d.; (17 items) (Folder 25.12)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — "The Play Pictorial,", n.d.; (17 p.) (Folder 25.13)
  - Dear Enemy; Me: A Book of Remembrance; "When Dreams Come True" — articles, reviews, etc., 1915-1916, n.d.; (12 items) (Folder 25.14)
  - Theater reviews and articles collected by JW, not of JW books or plays, 1914, n.d.; (14 items) (Folder 25.15)
  - Articles about "The Awakening," memorial to JW, May 1926-July 1927, n.d.; (10 items, originals) (Folder 26.1)
  - Articles about "The Awakening," memorial to JW, May 1926-July 1927, n.d.; (10 items, photocopies) (Folder 26.2)
  - Biographical clippings, articles, 1905-1908; (2 items) (Folder 26.3)
  - Biographical clippings, articles, 1907; (1 item, original) (Folder 26.4)
  - Biographical clippings, articles — jury duty, May 1909; (13 items) (Folder 26.5)
  - Biographical clippings, articles, Mar-Aug 1915; (8 items) (Folder 26.6)
  - Biographical clippings, articles — marriage, Sep 1915; (16 items) (Folder 26.7)
  - Biographical clippings, articles — death, June 1916; (47 items) (Folder 26.8)
  - Biographical clippings, articles — death, June-Sep 1916; (61 items) (Folder 26.9)
  - Biographical clippings, articles, including bibliography, 1916-1979, n.d.; (50 items) (Folder 26.10)
- Series V. Scrapbooks
  - When Patty Went to College and Just Patty — reviews, 1903, 1911 (Box 27)
  - The Wheat Princess — reviews, notices, 1905-1906 (Box 28)
  - Jerry Junior — reviews, notices, 1907 (Box 29)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — reviews and notices, and other notices of Jean Webster, Sep 1912-Nov 1915; (oversized) (Box 30)
  - Daddy Long-Legs — reviews and notices, and other notices of Jean Webster, Nov 1915-Jan 1916 (Box 31)
  - Dear Enemy — reviews, 1915-1916 (Box 32)
  - Me: A Book of Remembrance — reviews and notices, 1915-1916 (Box 32)
- Series VI. Business
  - General Business
    - Business — Professional correspondence, contracts, etc., 1909-1920; (21 items) (Folder 33.)
    - Business — Professional correspondence, contracts, etc., 1921-1940; (19 items) (Folder 33.2)
    - Business — Professional correspondence, contracts, etc., 1941-1949; (29 items) (Folder 33.3)
    - Business — Professional correspondence, contracts, etc., 1950-1972, n.d.; (7 items) (Folder 33.4)
  - Daddy Long-Legs Business
    - Professional correspondence, contracts, 1912-1913; (15 items) (Folder 33.5)
    - Weekly Gross, 1914-1916; (1 notebook, 25 p.) (Folder 33.6)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts incl. weekly box office receipts from Duke of York Theater, London, 1915-June 1916; (49 items) (Folder 33.7)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts incl. weekly box office receipts from Duke of York Theater, London, July 1916-Sep 1916; (48 items) (Folder 33.8)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts incl weekly box office receipts from Duke of York Theater, London, Oct 1916- Dec 1916; (28 items) (Folder 33.9)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts, 1917; (40 items) (Folder 34.1)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts, 1918; (21 items) (Folder 34.2)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts, 1919-1929; (48 items) (Folder 34.3)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts incl. contract between Glenn Ford McKinney and Fox Film Corporation, copies of Jean Webster's and Henry Miller's wills, 1930-1939; (38 items) (Folder 34.4)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts incl. contract between Jean McKinney Connor and 20th Century Fox Film Corporation, 1940-1941; (58 items) (Folder 34.5)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts, 1942-1949; (32 items) (Folder 34.6)
    - Professional correspondence, contracts incl. book jacket from 1967 edition of Daddy Long-Legs, 1950-1968, n.d.; (37 items) (Folder 34.7)
- Series VII. Personal Business
  - Personal Business — lease, invoices, etc. Farmers' Loan and Trust Corp., H.W. Baker Linen Co., Burrelle's Press Clipping Bureau, Brentano's, and August W. Mehler, Dealer in Meats, Poultry and Game, Dec 1914-May 1916; (29 items) (Folder 34.8)
  - Personal Business — cancelled checks Bank of the Metropolis, Mar-Oct 1914 (Folder 34.9)
  - Personal Business — cancelled checks Bank of the Metropolis, Jan 1915-Apr 1916 (Folder 34.10)
- Series VIII. Estate of Jean Webster
  - Estate — Jean Webster McKinney's Last Will and Testament, dated June 10, 1916; (4 copies) (Folder 35.1)
  - Estate — miscellaneous incl. cremation certificate, tax information, etc., June-Dec 1916; (6 items) (Folder 35.2)
  - Estate — correspondence, agreement between Ethelyn and Glenn Ford McKinney, and Rudolph Evans, sculptor, regarding "The Awakening," a memorial to Jean Webster, July 1924-Feb 1927, n.d.; (23 items) (Folder 35.3)
  - Estate — correspondence regarding Trust under Will of Jean Webster McKinney, Sep-Dec 1962; (40 items) (Folder 35.4)
- Series IX. Seances
  - Seances — miscellaneous material, correspondence, transcripts, etc., 1918-1925; (33 items) (Folder 35.5)
  - Seances — miscellaneous material, correspondence, transcripts, etc., (34 items) (Folder 35.6)
  - Seances — miscellaneous material, correspondence, transcripts, etc., (35 items) (Folder 35.7)
- Series X. Photographs
  - Jean Webster McKinney and Family
    - Jean Webster as a baby, with kindergarten class and with mother, 1876 - ca. 1882; (4 photos) (Folder 35.8)
    - School pictures, photo with a friend, Rolena Crowell, etc, ca. 1884 - ca. 1892; (9 photos, 2 signed by JW) (Folder 35.9)
    - Jean Webster at Lady Jane Grey School, 1894-1896; (6 photos) (Folder 35.10)
    - Jean Webster at Vassar — in graduation gown, 1901; (4 photos) (Folder 35.11)
    - Jean Webster at Vassar — in graduation gown, with Adelaide Crapsey on Class Day, and at 1911 reunion, 1901, 1911; (8 photos incl. ref. number 3.306) (Folder 35.12)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster — Photographer: Gifford, 1904; (4 photos) (Folder 36.1)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster — Photographer: Burr McIntosh Studio, 1906-1907; (1 photo) (Folder 36.2)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster — Photographer: Sol Young, 1909; (3 photos, 1 signed by JW) (Folder 36.3)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster in kilt, ca. 1911; (2 photos) (Folder 36.4)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, 1911; (3 photos, 1 signed by JW) (Folder 36.5)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, ca. 1912; (2 photos) (Folder 36.6)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster — half-length, in fur-collared coat, ca. 1914; (2 photos, ref. number 3.107) (Folder 36.7)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster — half-length, in fur-collared coat, ca. 1914; (1 oversized photo) (Folder 48.1)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster — Photographer: A. Spencer Beatty, ca. 1914; (2 photos) (Folder 36.8)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, standing at window — Photographer: A. Spencer Beatty, ca. 1915; (4 photos) (Folder 36.9)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, standing at window, ca. 1915; (1 oversized photo) (Folder 48.2)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, head and torso, wearing white, ca. 1915; (1 oversized photo, 13.75 x 10.25) (Folder 48.3)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, head and torso, wearing white, ca. 1915; (1 photo, oval framed, 3.25" x 2.75") (Folder 39.13)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, seated, light scarf around shoulders — Photographer: Aimé Dupont, ca. 1915; (5 photos) (Folder 36.10)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, seated, light scarf around shoulders — Photographer: Aimé Dupont, ca. 1915; (1 photo, oversized) (Folder 48.4)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, full-length, seated — Photographer: H.V. Furness, ca. 1915; (2 oversized photos) (Folder 48.5)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster and brother Sam Webster, ca. 1915; (1 glass plate positive, oversized, fragile) (Folder 48.14)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, half-length, seated, hands clasped, 1915; (3 photos, 1 signed by JW) (Folder 36.11)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster, half-length, seated, hands clasped, 1915; (1 photo, oversized) (Folder 48.6)
    - Portraits of Jean Webster, incl. pastoral scenes, Webster with cat, and Webster with dog, 1915; (5 photos) (Folder 36.12)
    - Jean Webster and dog, 1915; (1 photo, 8 x 5.75) (Folder 39.15)
    - Jean Webster standing, holding cat, 1915; (1 oversized photo) (Folder 48.7)
    - Jean Webster seated, holding cat, 1915; (1 oversized photo) (Folder 48.8)
    - Jean Webster and wheelbarrow, 1915; (1 photo) (Folder 36.13)
    - Jean Webster standing, holding walking stick, 1915; (1 photo) (Folder 36.13)
    - Jean Webster seated on a rock, holding walking stick, 1915; (1 photo) (Folder 36.13)
    - Jean Webster standing next to a tree, 1915; (1 photo) (Folder 36.13)
    - Jean Webster standing next to a creek, 1915; (1 photo) (Folder 36.13)
    - Jean Webster, seated, touching a tree, 1915; (1 photo) (Folder 36.13)
    - Jean Webster and wheelbarrow, 1915; (1 oversized photo) (Folder 48.9)
    - Jean Webster standing, holding walking stick, 1915; (1 oversized photo) (Folder 48.10)
    - Jean Webster seated on a rock, holding walking stick, 1915; (1 oversized photo) (Folder 48.11)
    - Jean Webster standing next to a tree, 1915; (1 oversized photo) (Folder 48.12)
    - Wedding of Jean Webster and Glenn Ford McKinney, 7 Sep 1915; (15 photos) (Folder 36.14)
    - Wedding of [Emily Westwood and Joe Lewis ?], (5 photos) (Folder 36.15)
    - "Ethelyn [McKinney] and Jean [Webster] at Barbizon,", (1 photo) (Folder 36.16)
    - Portraits of Jean Webster in rain gear, in overcoat and hat, in sweater and tie — Photographers: Sol Young and unknown, (4 photos) (Folder 36.17)
    - Portrait of Jean Webster in white blouse, n.d.; (1 oversized photo) (Folder 48.13)
    - Portraits of Jean Webster — Photographer: Clarence H. White, n.d.; (4 oversized photos) (Folder 48.15)
    - Photographs of Jean McKinney with father, Glenn Ford McKinney, on fourth birthday, etc., 1917-1920; (6 photos) (Folder 36.18)
    - Framed portrait of Annie Moffett Webster on her 90th birthday, 1942; (1 framed photo, 4.125" x 3.375") (Folder 39.14)
    - "The Awakening," memorial to Jean Webster, 1926-1927; (15 photos) (Folder 36.19)
    - "The Awakening," memorial to Jean Webster — laying sculpture in cemetery, 1926-1927; (6 photos) (Folder 36.20)
    - "The Awakening," memorial to Jean Webster, 1926-1927; (6 photos, negatives) (Folder 36.21)
  - Webster and McKinney Residences
    - Webster summer house in Far Rockaway, NY — interior and exterior, completed1887; (3 photos) (Folder 37.1)
    - "Interstrassen," Webster house in Fredonia, NY, n.d.; (7 photos) (Folder 37.2)
    - Tenth Street Studio, 43-55 W. 10th St. New York City, 1906; (1 photo) (Folder 37.3)
    - Tymor Farm, Union Vale, NY — purchased by Glenn Ford McKinney in 1913, dated 1909; (1 photo) (Folder 37.4)
    - Van Buren Point, Camp Phoenix — Glenn Ford McKinney's game preserve in Canada (?), ca. 1910; (5 photos) (Folder 37.5)
    - Tyringham, Massachusetts — 1911, 1913, 1914 summer residence of Jean Webster, n.d.; (13 photos, contact sheets/negatives of 41 photos) (Folder 37.6)
    - "Innisfree," the McKinney home in Greenwich, CT — Jean, Ethelyn McKinney, and Lena Weinstein in the Grape Arbor, (2 photos) (Folder 37.7)
    - Unidentified residences, n.d.; (2 photos) (Folder 37.8)
  - Schools
    - Lady Jane Grey School, Binghamton, NY, n.d.; (60 photographic reproductions from album of Jane Wadsworth Dowd, niece of the founder) (Folder 37.9)
    - Fredonia Normal School, n.d.; (1 photo) (Folder 37.10)
  - Trips Taken by Jean Webster McKinney
    - World Tour — Egypt — people, scenery, etc., Dec 1906; (10 photos) (Folder 37.11)
    - World Tour — India, Burma, Ceylon — people, scenery, etc., Dec 1906-Apr 1907; (24 photos) (Folder 37.12)
    - World Tour — India, Burma, Ceylon — people, scenery, etc., Dec 1906-Apr 1907; (47 photos) (Folder 38.1)
    - World Tour — India, Burma, Ceylon — Jean Webster, Lena Weinstein, Ethelyn McKinney, Aileen Ford McKinney, Mignonne Ford in various combinations and locations, Dec 1906-Apr 1907; (16 photos) (Folder 38.2)
    - World Tour — India — oversized photos, Dec 1906-Apr 1907; (7 oversized photos) (Box 49)
    - World Tour — Japan — people, scenery, etc., Apr-June1907; (36 photos) (Folder 38.3)
    - World Tour — Japan — Jean Webster, Lena Weinstein, Ethelyn McKinney, Aileen Ford McKinney, Mignonne Ford in various combinations and locations, Apr-June 1907; (42 photos) (Folder 38.4)
    - World Tour — Negatives (Folder 38.5)
    - Ireland — people, scenery, etc., summer 1912; (94 photos) (Folder 38.6)
    - Ireland — Jean Webster, Lena Weinstein, Ethelyn McKinney, Glenn Ford McKinney in various combinations and locations, summer 1912; (24 photos) (Folder 38.7)
    - Ireland — Negatives, summer 1912 (Folder 38.8)
  - Daddy Long-Legs
    - Jean Webster and children with Daddy Long-Legs doll, ca. 1914; (2 photos) (Folder 39.1)
    - Actresses in Daddy Long-Legs — Renee Kelly, Margaret Field, (4 photos, 1 negative) (Folder 39.2)
    - Oversized photos of Daddy Long-Legs: Ruth Chatterton, autographed photo, photos of scenes from Chatterton-Miller production, n.d.; (26 oversized photos) (Box 50)
- Series XI. Memorabilia
  - Jean Webster McKinney and Family
    - Biographical Material
      - Genealogy of Samuel Clemens' immediate family — family tree, n.d.; (1 item (oversized) (Folder 51.5)
      - Biography of Jean Webster as it appears in the Book of Enduring Names of Town Hall, Inc., incl. letter to Jean McKinney Connor from Town Hall, Inc., Nov 1946, (2 oversized items ) (Folder 51.4)
      - Pages from family Bible — records of Clemens, Moffett, Webster, and McKinney families, (3 p.) (Folder 39.3)